<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
  <id>kbibtex.desktop</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0+</project_license>
  <name>KBibTeX</name>
  <name xml:lang="cs">KBibTeX</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">KBibTeX</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt">KBibTeX</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt-BR">KBibTeX</name>
  <name xml:lang="sk">KBibTeX</name>
  <name xml:lang="sv">Kbibtex</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">KBibTeX</name>
  <name xml:lang="x-test">xxKBibTeXxx</name>
  <summary>BibTeX editor for KDE to edit bibliographies used with LaTeX</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt">O BibTeX é um editor para o KDE, onde se podem editar bibliografias usadas com o LaTeX</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt-BR">BibTeX é um editor para o KDE, onde se podem editar bibliografias usadas com o LaTeX</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sk">Editor BibTeX pre KDE na editáciu použitých bibliografií s LaTeXom</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sv">Bibtex-editor för KDE för att redigera bibliografier använda med Latex</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Редактор BibTeX для KDE. Призначений для редагування бібліографій, що використовуються у LaTeX.</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="x-test">xxBibTeX editor for KDE to edit bibliographies used with LaTeXxx</summary>
  <description>
    <p>
      KBibTeX is a reference management application which can be used to collect TeX/LaTeX bibliographies and export them in various formats.
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">O KBibTeX é uma aplicação de gestão de referências que pode ser usada para recolher as bibliografias de TeX/LaTeX e exportá-las em vários formatos.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt-BR">KBibTeX é um aplicativo para gerenciamento de referências que pode ser usado para coletar as bibliografias TeX/LaTeX e exportá-las para vários formatos.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sk">KBibTeX je aplikácia na správu referencií, ktorú je možné použiť na zbieranie bibliografií TeX/LaTeX a exportovať ich v rôznych formátoch.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Kbibtex är ett referenshanteringsprogram som kan användas för att samla Tex/Latex-bibliografier och exportera dem med diverse format.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">KBibTeX — програма для керування посиланнями, якою можна скористатися для створення бібліографій TeX/LaTeX та експортування даних бібліографій у різноманітних форматах.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxKBibTeX is a reference management application which can be used to collect TeX/LaTeX bibliographies and export them in various formats.xx</p>
    <p>KBibTeX can do the following things:</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">O KBibTeX pode fazer as seguintes coisas:</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt-BR">O KBibTeX pode fazer o seguinte:</p>
    <p xml:lang="sk">KBibTeX dokáže nasledovné veci:</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Kbibtex kan göra följande saker:</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">KBibTeX може виконувати такі завдання:</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxKBibTeX can do the following things:xx</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Preview bibliography entries in various formats (Source (BibTeX), Source (RIS), Wikipedia, standard (XML/XSLT), fancy (XML/XSLT), and abstract-only (XML/XSLT)). Additional preview styles become available when bibtex2html is installed.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Antever os itens bibliográficos em diversos formatos (Código (BibTeX), Código (RIS), Wikipédia, normal (XML/XSLT), bonito (XML/XSLT) e apenas o resumo (XML/XSLT)). Ficam disponíveis mais estilos de antevisão quando instalar o 'bibtex2html'.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Visualizar os itens bibliográficos em diversos formatos (Código (BibTeX), Código (RIS), Wikipédia, normal (XML/XSLT), bonito (XML/XSLT) e apenas resumo (XML/XSLT)). Ficam disponíveis mais estilos de visualização quando o 'bibtex2html' estiver instalado.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Vytvoriť náhľad bibliografií v rôznych formátoch (zdroj (BibTeX), zdroj (RIS), Wikipédia, štandard (XML/XSLT), pekné (XML/XSLT), a iba abstraktné (XML/XSLT)). Dodatočné štýly je možné použiť po inštalácii bibtex2html.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Förhandsgranska bibliografier med olika format (källa (Bibtex), källa (RIS), Wikipedia, standard (XML/XSLT), snygg (XML/XSLT) och bara sammandrag (XML/XSLT)). Ytterligare förhandsgranskningsstilar är tillgängliga om bibtex2html är installerat.</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Виконувати попередній перегляд і зберігати записи бібліографії у різних форматах (початковий код (BibTeX), початковий код (RIS), Вікіпедія, standard (XML/XSLT), fancy (XML/XSLT) та abstract-only (XML/XSLT)). Доступ до додаткових стилів попереднього перегляду можна отримати після встановлення програми bibtex2html.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxPreview bibliography entries in various formats (Source (BibTeX), Source (RIS), Wikipedia, standard (XML/XSLT), fancy (XML/XSLT), and abstract-only (XML/XSLT)). Additional preview styles become available when bibtex2html is installed.xx</li>
      <li>Import data in various bibliography file formats such as BibTeX, RIS and ISI (requires bibutils) and export data to PDF (requires pdflatex), PostScript (requires latex), RTF (requires latex2rtf), and HTML.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Importar os dados em diversos formatos de ficheiros bibliográficos, como o BibTeX, RIS e ISI (precisa das 'bibutils') e exportar os dados para PDF (precisa do 'pdflatex'), PostScript (precisa do 'latex'), RTF (precisa do 'latex2rtf') e HTML.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Importar os dados em diversos formatos de arquivos bibliográficos, como o BibTeX, RIS e ISI (precisa da 'bibutils') e exportar os dados para PDF (precisa do 'pdflatex'), PostScript (precisa do 'latex'), RTF (precisa do 'latex2rtf') e HTML.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Importovať údaje v rôznych bibliografických súborových formátoch ako BibTeX, RIS a ISI (vyžaduje bibutils) a exportovať údaje do PDF (vyžaduje pdflatex), PostScript (vyžaduje latex), RTF (vyžaduje latex2rtf) a HTML.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Importera data med diverse bibliografi-filformat såsom Bibtex, RIS och ISI (kräver bibutils) och exportera data till PDF (kräver pdflatex), PostScript (kräver latex), RTF (kräver latex2rtf), och HTML.</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Імпортувати дані у різноманітних форматах файлів бібліографії, зокрема BibTeX, RIS та ISI (слід встановити bibutils) та експортувати дані до PDF (потребує встановлення pdflatex), PostScript (потребує встановлення latex), RTF (потребує встановлення latex2rtf) та HTML.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxImport data in various bibliography file formats such as BibTeX, RIS and ISI (requires bibutils) and export data to PDF (requires pdflatex), PostScript (requires latex), RTF (requires latex2rtf), and HTML.xx</li>
      <li>Search for the bibliography entries data in online databases (e.g. Google Scholar, ACM, IEEE, arXiv, etc.)</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Procurar por dados de itens bibliográficos nas bases de dados 'online' (p.ex. Google Scholar, ACM, IEEE, arXiv, etc.)</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Procurar por dados de itens bibliográficos nos banco de dados online (p.ex., Google Scholar, ACM, IEEE, arXiv, etc.)</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Hľadať dáta položkie bibliografie v online databázach (napr. Google Scholar, ACM, IEEE, arXiv, atď.)</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Söka efter bibliografiposternas data i databaser på nätet (t.ex. Google Scholar, ACM, IEEE, arXiv, etc.)</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Виконувати пошук даних записів бібліографії у базах даних у інтернеті (зокрема у Google Scholar, ACM, IEEE, arXiv тощо).</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxSearch for the bibliography entries data in online databases (e.g. Google Scholar, ACM, IEEE, arXiv, etc.)xx</li>
      <li>Preview local or remote (online) resources, e.g. PDF files, linked in the BibTEX entry.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Fazer uma antevisão dos recursos locais ou remotos ('online'), p.ex. ficheiros PDF, associada aos itens do BibTEX.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Visualizar os recursos locais ou remotos (online), p.ex., arquivos PDF, associados aos itens do BibTEX.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Vytvoriť náhľad miestnych alebo vzdialených (online) zdrojov, napr. PDF súborov, odkázaných v položke BibTEX.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Förhandsgranska lokala eller fjärresurser (på nätet), t.ex. PDF-filer, länkade i Bibtex-posten.</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Попередньо переглядати локальні та інтернет-ресурси, зокрема файли PDF, пов’язані із записом бібліографії BibTeX.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxPreview local or remote (online) resources, e.g. PDF files, linked in the BibTEX entry.xx</li>
      <li>Find and merge duplicate entries in bibliography.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Procurar e reunir itens duplicados na bibliografia.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Procurar e mesclar os itens duplicados na bibliografia.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Nájsť a zlúčiť duplicitné položky v bibliografii.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Hitta och sammanfoga duplicerade poster i bibliografin.</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Шукати і об’єднувати дублікати записів у бібліографії.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxFind and merge duplicate entries in bibliography.xx</li>
      <li>Integrate your bibliographies with LaTeX editors such as Kile and LyX.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Integrar as suas bibliografias com os editores de LaTeX, como o Kile e o LyX.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Integrar suas bibliografias com os editores de LaTeX, como o Kile e o LyX.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Integrovať vaše bibliografie s editormi LaTeX ako Kile a LyX.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Integrera bibliografierna med Latex-editorer såsom Kile och LyX</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Інтегрувати ваші бібліографії з редакторами LaTeX, зокрема Kile та LyX.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxIntegrate your bibliographies with LaTeX editors such as Kile and LyX.xx</li>
      <li>Import your Zotero library.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Importar a sua biblioteca do Zotero.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Importar sua biblioteca do Zotero.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Importovať vašu knižnicu Zotero.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Importera ett Zotero-bibliotek.</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Імпортувати дані з вашої бібліотеки Zotero.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxImport your Zotero library.xx</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <url type="homepage">http://home.gna.org/kbibtex/</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugs.kde.org/enter_bug.cgi?format=guided&amp;product=kbibtex</url>
  <url type="help">http://docs.kde.org/development/en/extragear-office/kbibtex/index.html</url>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>http://home.gna.org/kbibtex/screenshots/kbibtex-20110213.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <project_group>KDE</project_group>
  <provides>
    <binary>kbibtex</binary>
  </provides>
</component>
