<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
  <id>org.kde.kbibtex.desktop</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0+</project_license>
  <name>KBibTeX</name>
  <name xml:lang="ast">KBibTeX</name>
  <name xml:lang="bs">KBibTeX</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">KBibTeX</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca-valencia">KBibTeX</name>
  <name xml:lang="cs">KBibTeX</name>
  <name xml:lang="de">KBibTeX</name>
  <name xml:lang="en-GB">KBibTeX</name>
  <name xml:lang="es">KBibTeX</name>
  <name xml:lang="fi">KBibTeX</name>
  <name xml:lang="fr">KBibTeX</name>
  <name xml:lang="gl">KBibTeX</name>
  <name xml:lang="it">KBibTeX</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">KBibTeX</name>
  <name xml:lang="pl">KBibTeX</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt">KBibTeX</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt-BR">KBibTeX</name>
  <name xml:lang="ru">KBibTeX</name>
  <name xml:lang="sk">KBibTeX</name>
  <name xml:lang="sv">Kbibtex</name>
  <name xml:lang="tr">KBibTeX</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">KBibTeX</name>
  <name xml:lang="x-test">xxKBibTeXxx</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh-CN">KBibTeX</name>
  <summary>BibTeX editor by KDE to edit bibliographies used with LaTeX</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca">Editor de BibTeX, creat per la comunitat KDE, per editar bibliografies emprant LaTeX</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca-valencia">Editor de BibTeX, creat per la comunitat KDE, per editar bibliografies emprant LaTeX</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="de">BibTeX-Editor von KDE zum Bearbeiten von Bibliografien mit LaTeX</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="en-GB">BibTeX editor by KDE to edit bibliographies used with LaTeX</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="es">Editor de BibTeX creado por KDE para editar las bibliografías usadas con LaTeX</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fi">KDE:n BibTeX-muokkain LaTeXissa käytettävien lähdeluettelojen muokkaamiseen</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fr">Éditeur BixTeX par KDE pour modifier des bibliographies utilisées avec LaTeX</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="gl">Editor de BibTeX de KDE, para editar bibliografías que se usen con LaTeX</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="it">Editor BibTeX di KDE per la modifica delle bibliografie usate con LaTeX</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">BibTeX-bewerker door KDE om bibliografieën te bewerken gebruikt met LaTeX</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pl">Edytor BibTeX autorstwa KDE do edytowania bibliografii używanych w edytorach LaTeX</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt">O BibTeX é um editor do KDE, onde se podem editar bibliografias usadas com o LaTeX</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sk">Editor BibTeX pre KDE na editáciu použitých bibliografií s LaTeXom</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sv">Bibtex-editor av KDE för att redigera bibliografier använda med Latex</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="tr">Kaynakça dosyalarını LaTeX kullanarak düzenlemek için KDE BibTeX düzenleyicisi</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Редактор BibTeX від KDE. Призначений для редагування бібліографій, що використовуються у LaTeX.</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="x-test">xxBibTeX editor by KDE to edit bibliographies used with LaTeXxx</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh-CN">KDE 提供的 BibTeX 编辑器，用来编辑 LaTeX 使用的参考文献目录</summary>
  <description>
    <p>
      KBibTeX is a reference management application which can be used to collect TeX/LaTeX bibliographies and export them in various formats.
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="bs">KBibTeX je aplikacija za upravljanje referencom koja može biti upotrijebljena za skupljanje TeX/LaTeX bibliografijama i izvoziti ih u raznim formatima.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">El KBibTeX és una aplicació per a la gestió de referències que es pot utilitzar per recollir bibliografies en TeX/LaTeX i exportar-les a diversos formats.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">El KBibTeX és una aplicació per a la gestió de referències que es pot utilitzar per recollir bibliografies en TeX/LaTeX i exportar-les a diversos formats.</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">KBibTeX ist ein Programm zur Verwaltung von Referenzen und kann dazu benutzt werden, TeX/LaTeX-Bibliografien zusammenzustellen und sie in verschiedenen Formaten zu exportieren.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">KBibTeX is a reference management application which can be used to collect TeX/LaTeX bibliographies and export them in various formats.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">KBibTeX es una aplicación de gestión de referencias que se puede utilizar para recoger bibliografías TeX/LaTeX y exportarlas en varios formatos.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fi">KBibTeX on viitteidenhallintasovellus, jolla voi koota TeX/LaTeX-lähdeluetteloita ja viedä niitä eri tiedostomuotoihin.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">KBibTeX est une application de gestion de références qui peut être utilisée pour collecter des bibliographies TeX/LaTeX et les exporter dans divers formats.</p>
    <p xml:lang="gl">KBibTeX é un aplicativo de xestión de referencias que pode usar para recoller bibliografías de TeX/LaTeX e exportalas en diversos formatos.</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">KBibTeX è un'applicazione di gestione delle fonti che può essere utilizzata per radunare bibliografie TeX/LaTeX ed esportarle in vari formati.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">KBibTeX is een toepassing voor beheer van referenties die gebruikt kunnen worden om TeX/LaTeX bibliografieën te verzamelen en te exporteren in verschillende formaten.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">KBibTeX jest programem do zarządzania odsyłaczami, którego można użyć do zbierania bibliografii TeX/LaTeX i eksportowania ich w różnych postaciach.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">O KBibTeX é uma aplicação de gestão de referências que pode ser usada para recolher as bibliografias de TeX/LaTeX e exportá-las em vários formatos.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt-BR">KBibTeX é um aplicativo para gerenciamento de referências que pode ser usado para coletar as bibliografias TeX/LaTeX e exportá-las para vários formatos.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sk">KBibTeX je aplikácia na správu referencií, ktorú je možné použiť na zbieranie bibliografií TeX/LaTeX a exportovať ich v rôznych formátoch.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Kbibtex är ett referenshanteringsprogram som kan användas för att samla Tex/Latex-bibliografier och exportera dem med diverse format.</p>
    <p xml:lang="tr">KBibTex, TeX/LaTeX kaynakçalarını toplamak ve çeşitli formatlarda dışa aktarmak için kullanılabilecek bir başvuru yönetim uygulamasıdır.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">KBibTeX — програма для керування посиланнями, якою можна скористатися для створення бібліографій TeX/LaTeX та експортування даних бібліографій у різноманітних форматах.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxKBibTeX is a reference management application which can be used to collect TeX/LaTeX bibliographies and export them in various formats.xx</p>
    <p>KBibTeX can do the following things:</p>
    <p xml:lang="bs">KBibTeX može uraditi sljedeće stvari:</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">KBibTeX pot fer les següents coses:</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">KBibTeX pot fer les següents coses:</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">Mit KBibTeX können Sie folgende Aufgabe erledigen:</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">KBibTeX can do the following things:</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">KBibTeX puede hacer las siguientes tareas:</p>
    <p xml:lang="fi">KBibTeXilla voit tehdä seuraavia asioita:</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">KBibTeX peut faire les choses suivantes : </p>
    <p xml:lang="gl">KBibTeX pode facer o seguinte:</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">KBibTeX è in grado di svolgere i seguenti compiti:</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">KBibTeX kan de volgende dingen:</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">KBibTeX ma następujące możliwości:</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">O KBibTeX pode fazer as seguintes coisas:</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt-BR">O KBibTeX pode fazer o seguinte:</p>
    <p xml:lang="sk">KBibTeX dokáže nasledovné veci:</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Kbibtex kan göra följande saker:</p>
    <p xml:lang="tr">KBibTex aşağıdakileri yapabilir:</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">KBibTeX може виконувати такі завдання:</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxKBibTeX can do the following things:xx</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh-CN">KBibTeX 可以完成以下工作：</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Preview bibliography entries in various formats (Source (BibTeX), Source (RIS), Wikipedia, standard (XML/XSLT), fancy (XML/XSLT), and abstract-only (XML/XSLT)). Additional preview styles become available when bibtex2html is installed.</li>
      <li xml:lang="bs">Pregled ulaza bibliografija u raznim formatima (Source(BibTeX), Source(RIS), Wikipedia, standard(XML/XSLT), fancy(XML/XSLT) i abstract-only(XML/XSLT)). Dodatni pregled stilova postaje dostupan kada je bibtex2html instaliran.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Vista prèvia de les entrades a la bibliografia en diversos formats (Origen (BibTeX), Origen (RIS), Viquipèdia, estàndard (XML/XSLT), elaborat (XML/XSLT), i només el resum (XML/XSLT)). Hi ha disponibles estils de vista prèvia addicionals quan s'instal·la «bibtex2html».</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Vista prèvia de les entrades a la bibliografia en diversos formats (Origen (BibTeX), Origen (RIS), Viquipèdia, estàndard (XML/XSLT), elaborat (XML/XSLT), i només el resum (XML/XSLT)). Hi ha disponibles estils de vista prèvia addicionals quan s'instal·la «bibtex2html».</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Vorschau und Speichern von Bibliografie-Einträgen in verschiedenen Formaten (Quelltext (BibTeX), Quelltext (RIS), Wikipedia, Standard (XML/XSLT), fancy (XML/XSLT) und abstract-only (XML/XSLT)). Zusätzliche Vorschaustile sind verfügbar, wenn Sie „bibtex2html“ installiert haben.</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Preview bibliography entries in various formats (Source (BibTeX), Source (RIS), Wikipedia, standard (XML/XSLT), fancy (XML/XSLT), and abstract-only (XML/XSLT)). Additional preview styles become available when bibtex2html is installed.</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Previsualizar las entradas de bibliografías en varios formatos (Fuente (BibTeX), fuente (RIS), Wikipedia, estándar (XML/XSLT), elegante (XML/XSLT), y solo abstracto (XML/XSLT)). Al instalar bibtex2html dispondrá de estilos de previsualización adicionales.</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">Esikatsella lähdetietueita eri muodoissa (BibTeX- tai RIS-lähdekoodina, Wikipedia-muodossa, vakio- tai tyylitellyssä muodossa (XML/XSLT) sekä vain tiivistelminä (XML/XSLT)). Lisäesikatselutyylit tulevat käyttöön, kun bibtex2html on asennettu.</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Prévisualiser des entrées bibliographiques dans divers formats (Source (BibTeX), Source (RIS), Wikipédia, standard (XML/XSLT), sophistiqué (XML/XSLT), et abstrait (XML/XSLT)). Des styles d'aperçus supplémentaires sont disponibles après de l'installation de bibtex2html.</li>
      <li xml:lang="gl">Obteña unha vista previa de entradas bibliográficas en varios formatos: fonte (BibTeX ou RIS), Wikipedia, estándar (XML/XSLT), elegante (XML/XSLT), e só resumo (XML/XSLT). Se ten «bibtex2html» instalado, disporá de estilos de vista previa adicionais.</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Visualizzare in anteprima le voci bibliografiche in vari formati (Source (BibTeX), Source (RIS), Wikipedia, standard (XML/XSLT), fancy (XML/XSLT), e in formato solo sommario (XML/XSLT)). Saranno disponibili stili aggiuntivi di anteprima se si installa il pacchetto bibtex2html.</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Bibliografische items bekijken in verschillende formaten (bron (BibTeX), bron (RIS), Wikipedia, standaard (XML/XSLT), fancy (XML/XSLT) en alleen abstract (XML/XSLT)). Extra stijlen voor bekijken komen beschikbaar wanneer bibtex2html is geïnstalleerd.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Podgląd wpisów bibliograficznych w rozmaitych formatach (Source (BibTeX), Source (RIS), Wikipedia, standard (XML/XSLT), elegancki (XML/XSLT) i tylko streszczenia (XML/XSLT)). Dodatkowo, dostępne stają się style podglądu, gdy wgrany jest pakiet bibtex2html.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Antever os itens bibliográficos em diversos formatos (Código (BibTeX), Código (RIS), Wikipédia, normal (XML/XSLT), bonito (XML/XSLT) e apenas o resumo (XML/XSLT)). Ficam disponíveis mais estilos de antevisão quando instalar o 'bibtex2html'.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Visualizar os itens bibliográficos em diversos formatos (Código (BibTeX), Código (RIS), Wikipédia, normal (XML/XSLT), bonito (XML/XSLT) e apenas resumo (XML/XSLT)). Ficam disponíveis mais estilos de visualização quando o 'bibtex2html' estiver instalado.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Vytvoriť náhľad bibliografií v rôznych formátoch (zdroj (BibTeX), zdroj (RIS), Wikipédia, štandard (XML/XSLT), pekné (XML/XSLT), a iba abstraktné (XML/XSLT)). Dodatočné štýly je možné použiť po inštalácii bibtex2html.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Förhandsgranska bibliografier med olika format (källa (Bibtex), källa (RIS), Wikipedia, standard (XML/XSLT), snygg (XML/XSLT) och bara sammandrag (XML/XSLT)). Ytterligare förhandsgranskningsstilar är tillgängliga om bibtex2html är installerat.</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">Kaynakça girdilerini çeşitli biçimlerde önizleyin Kaynak (BibTeX), Kaynak (RIS), Wikipedia, standart (XML/XSLT), süslü (XML/XSLT) ve salt özet (XML/XSLT). Bibtex2html kurulduğunda ek önizleme stilleri kullanılabilir hale gelir.</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Виконувати попередній перегляд і зберігати записи бібліографії у різних форматах (початковий код (BibTeX), початковий код (RIS), Вікіпедія, standard (XML/XSLT), fancy (XML/XSLT) та abstract-only (XML/XSLT)). Доступ до додаткових стилів попереднього перегляду можна отримати після встановлення програми bibtex2html.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxPreview bibliography entries in various formats (Source (BibTeX), Source (RIS), Wikipedia, standard (XML/XSLT), fancy (XML/XSLT), and abstract-only (XML/XSLT)). Additional preview styles become available when bibtex2html is installed.xx</li>
      <li>Import data in various bibliography file formats such as BibTeX, RIS and ISI (requires bibutils) and export data to PDF (requires pdflatex), PostScript (requires latex), RTF (requires latex2rtf), and HTML.</li>
      <li xml:lang="bs">Uvoz podataka u raznim bibliografskim formatima datoteke kao što su BibTeX, RIS i ISI (zahtijeva bibutils) i izvoz podataka u PDF(zahtijeva pdflatex), PostScript(zahtijeva latex), RTF(zahtijeva latex2rtf) i HTML.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Importar les dades en diversos formats de fitxer per a bibliografies, tals com BibTeX, RIS i ISI (requereix «bibutils») i exporta les dades a PDF (requereix «pdflatex»), PostScript (requereix «latex»), RTF (requereix «latex2rtf»), i HTML.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Importar les dades en diversos formats de fitxer per a bibliografies, tals com BibTeX, RIS i ISI (requereix «bibutils») i exporta les dades a PDF (requereix «pdflatex»), PostScript (requereix «latex»), RTF (requereix «latex2rtf»), i HTML.</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Import von Daten aus verschiedenen Bibliografie-Dateiformaten wie BibTeX, RIS und ISI (benötigt bibutils) und Export von Daten in die Formate PDF (benötigt pdflatex), PostScript (benötigt latex), RTF (benötigt latex2rtf) und HTML.</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Import data in various bibliography file formats such as BibTeX, RIS and ISI (requires bibutils) and export data to PDF (requires pdflatex), PostScript (requires latex), RTF (requires latex2rtf), and HTML.</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Importa datos en varios formatos de archivo de bibliografía, como por ejemplo BibTeX, RIS y ISI (requiere bibutils) y exporta datos a PDF (requiere pdflatex), PostScript (requiere latex), RTF (requiere latex2rtf), y HTML.</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">Tuoda tietoja eri lähdetietokantamuodoista kuten BibTeXistä, RISistä tai ISIstä (vaatii bibutils-paketin) sekä viedä tietoja PDF:ksi (vaatii pdflatexin), PostScriptiksi (vaatii latexin), RTF:ksi (vaatii latex2rtf:n) tai HTML:ksi.</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Importer des données dans divers formats de fichiers bibliographiques comme BibTeX, RIS, ISI (nécessite bibutils) et exporter des données en PDF (nécessite pdflatex), PostScript (nécessite latex), RTF (nécessite latex2rtf), et HTML.</li>
      <li xml:lang="gl">Importe datos in varios formatos de ficheiro bibliográficos como BibTeX, RIS e ISI (require «bibutils») e exporte os datos a PDF (require «pdflatex»), PostScript (require «latex»), RTF (require «latex2rtf»), e HTML.</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Importare i dati in vari formati di file bibliografici, come BibTeX, RIS e ISI (richiede bibutils), ed esportare i dati in PDF (richiede pdflatex), PostScript (richiede latex), RTF (richiede latex2rtf) e HTML.</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Gegevens importeren in verschillende bestandsformaten voor bibliografieën zoals BibTeX, RIS en ISI (vereist bibutils) en exporteert gegevens naar PDF (vereist pdflatex), PostScript (vereist latex), RTF (vereist latex2rtf), en HTML.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Importowanie danych w rozmaitych formatach plików bibliografii takich jak BibTeX, RIS oraz ISI (wymaga bibutils) i eksportowanie danych do PDF (wymaga pdflatex), PostScript (wymaga latex), RTF (wymaga latex2rtf) oraz HTML.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Importar os dados em diversos formatos de ficheiros bibliográficos, como o BibTeX, RIS e ISI (precisa das 'bibutils') e exportar os dados para PDF (precisa do 'pdflatex'), PostScript (precisa do 'latex'), RTF (precisa do 'latex2rtf') e HTML.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Importar os dados em diversos formatos de arquivos bibliográficos, como o BibTeX, RIS e ISI (precisa da 'bibutils') e exportar os dados para PDF (precisa do 'pdflatex'), PostScript (precisa do 'latex'), RTF (precisa do 'latex2rtf') e HTML.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Importovať údaje v rôznych bibliografických súborových formátoch ako BibTeX, RIS a ISI (vyžaduje bibutils) a exportovať údaje do PDF (vyžaduje pdflatex), PostScript (vyžaduje latex), RTF (vyžaduje latex2rtf) a HTML.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Importera data med diverse bibliografi-filformat såsom Bibtex, RIS och ISI (kräver bibutils) och exportera data till PDF (kräver pdflatex), PostScript (kräver latex), RTF (kräver latex2rtf), och HTML.</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">BibTeX, RIS ve ISI (bibutils gerektirir) gibi çeşitli kaynakça dosya formatlarına verileri içe aktarın ve PDF  (pdflatex gerektirir), PostScript (lateks gerektirir), RTF (latex2rtf gerektirir) ve HTML'e verileri dışa aktarın.</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Імпортувати дані у різноманітних форматах файлів бібліографії, зокрема BibTeX, RIS та ISI (слід встановити bibutils) та експортувати дані до PDF (потребує встановлення pdflatex), PostScript (потребує встановлення latex), RTF (потребує встановлення latex2rtf) та HTML.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxImport data in various bibliography file formats such as BibTeX, RIS and ISI (requires bibutils) and export data to PDF (requires pdflatex), PostScript (requires latex), RTF (requires latex2rtf), and HTML.xx</li>
      <li>Search for the bibliography entries data in online databases (e.g. Google Scholar, ACM, IEEE, arXiv, etc.)</li>
      <li xml:lang="bs">Pretraga za ulazne podatke bibliografije u online bazama podataka (npr. Google Scholar, ACM, IEEE,arXiv, itd.)</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Cerca dades d'entrades bibliogràfiques a les bases de dades en línia (p. ex., Google Scholar, ACM, IEEE, arXiv, etc.)</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Cerca dades d'entrades bibliogràfiques a les bases de dades en línia (p. ex., Google Scholar, ACM, IEEE, arXiv, etc.)</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Suche nach Daten mit Bibliografie-Einträgen in Online-Datenbanken (z. B. Google Scholar, ACM, IEEE, arXiv, usw.)</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Search for the bibliography entries data in online databases (e.g. Google Scholar, ACM, IEEE, arXiv, etc.)</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Busca datos de las entradas bibliográficas en bases de datos en línea (por ejemplo Google Scholar, ACM, IEEE, arXiv, etc.)</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">Etsiä lähdetietueiden tietoja verkon tietokannoista (Google Scholarista, ACM:stä, IEEE:stä, arXivista jne.)</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Rechercher des entrées bibliographiques dans des banques de données en ligne (par exemple Google Scholar, ACM, IEEE, arXiv, etc.)</li>
      <li xml:lang="gl">Busque os datos das entradas bibliográficas en base de datos en internet (como Google Scholar, ACM, IEEE, arXiv, etc.).</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Ricercare voci bibliografiche nei database in linea (per es., Google Scholar, ACM, IEEE, arXiv, ecc.)</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Zoeken naar bibliografie-items in online databases (bijv. Google Scholar, ACM, IEEE, arXiv, etc.)</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Wyszukiwanie wpisów bibliograficznych w bazach internetowych (np. Google Scholar, ACM, IEEE, arXiv, itp.)</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Procurar por dados de itens bibliográficos nas bases de dados 'online' (p.ex. Google Scholar, ACM, IEEE, arXiv, etc.)</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Procurar por dados de itens bibliográficos nos banco de dados online (p.ex., Google Scholar, ACM, IEEE, arXiv, etc.)</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Hľadať dáta položkie bibliografie v online databázach (napr. Google Scholar, ACM, IEEE, arXiv, atď.)</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Söka efter bibliografiposternas data i databaser på nätet (t.ex. Google Scholar, ACM, IEEE, arXiv, etc.)</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">Çevrimiçi veritabanlarında kaynakça girdi verilerini arayın (Ör. Google Scholar, ACM, IEEE, arXiv, vb.)</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Виконувати пошук даних записів бібліографії у базах даних у інтернеті (зокрема у Google Scholar, ACM, IEEE, arXiv тощо).</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxSearch for the bibliography entries data in online databases (e.g. Google Scholar, ACM, IEEE, arXiv, etc.)xx</li>
      <li>Preview local or remote (online) resources, e.g. PDF files, linked in the BibTEX entry.</li>
      <li xml:lang="bs">Pregled lokalnih ili udaljenih (online) resursa , npr. PDF datoteke, povezane u BibTEX ulazu.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Vista prèvia de recursos locals o remots (connectats), p. ex., fitxers PDF, vinculats amb l'entrada de BibTeX.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Vista prèvia de recursos locals o remots (connectats), p. ex., fitxers PDF, vinculats amb l'entrada de BibTeX.</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Anzeige von lokalen und entfernten (Online-) Ressourcen wie zum Beispiel PDF-Dateien, die mit einem BibTEX Eintrag verknüpft sind.</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Preview local or remote (online) resources, e.g. PDF files, linked in the BibTEX entry.</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Previsualiza los recursos locales o remotos (en línea), por ejemplo archivos PDF, que estén enlazados en una entrada BibTEX.</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">Esikatsella BibTeX-tietueeseen kytkettyjä paikallisia tai etäresursseja, esim. PDF-tiedostoja.</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Prévisualiser des ressources locales ou distantes (en ligne), par exemple des fichiers PDF ou des liens dans l'entrée BibTeX.</li>
      <li xml:lang="gl">Obteña unha vista previa de recursos locais ou en internet, como ficheiros PDF, que estean ligados desde a entrada de BibTeX.</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Visualizzare in anteprima risorse locali o remote (in linea), per es. file PDF, collegate nella voce BibTEX.</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Bekijken van lokale hulpbronnen of op afstand (online), bijv. PDF-bestanden, gekoppeld in het BibTEX-item.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Podgląd lokalnych lub zdalnych (internetowych) zasobów, np. plików PDF, do których odwołuje się wpis BibTEX.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Fazer uma antevisão dos recursos locais ou remotos ('online'), p.ex. ficheiros PDF, associada aos itens do BibTEX.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Visualizar os recursos locais ou remotos (online), p.ex., arquivos PDF, associados aos itens do BibTEX.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Vytvoriť náhľad miestnych alebo vzdialených (online) zdrojov, napr. PDF súborov, odkázaných v položke BibTEX.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Förhandsgranska lokala eller fjärresurser (på nätet), t.ex. PDF-filer, länkade i Bibtex-posten.</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">Yerel veya uzak (çevrimiçi) kaynakları önizleyin, ör. BibTEX girdisinde bağlantı verilen PDF dosyaları.</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Попередньо переглядати локальні та інтернет-ресурси, зокрема файли PDF, пов’язані із записом бібліографії BibTeX.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxPreview local or remote (online) resources, e.g. PDF files, linked in the BibTEX entry.xx</li>
      <li>Find and merge duplicate entries in bibliography.</li>
      <li xml:lang="bs">Potraži i spoji duplikate ulaza u bibliografiju.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Troba i fusiona les entrades duplicades a la bibliografia.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Troba i fusiona les entrades duplicades a la bibliografia.</li>
      <li xml:lang="de"> Suchen und zusammenführen von doppelten Einträgen in Bibliografien.</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Find and merge duplicate entries in bibliography.</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Busca y fusiona las entradas duplicadas en la bibliografía.</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">Etsiä ja yhdistää lähdetietueiden kaksoiskappaleita.</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Trouver et fusionner des doublons dans les entrées bibliographiques.</li>
      <li xml:lang="gl">Atope e fusione entradas duplicadas da bibliografía.</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Trovare e unire voci duplicate nella bibliografia.</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Zoek en voeg dubbele items in de bibliografie samen.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Znajdywanie i scalanie powielonych wpisów w bibliografii.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Procurar e reunir itens duplicados na bibliografia.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Procurar e mesclar os itens duplicados na bibliografia.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Nájsť a zlúčiť duplicitné položky v bibliografii.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Hitta och sammanfoga duplicerade poster i bibliografin.</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">Kaynakçadaki yinelenen girişleri bulun ve birleştirin.</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Шукати і об’єднувати дублікати записів у бібліографії.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxFind and merge duplicate entries in bibliography.xx</li>
      <li>Integrate your bibliographies with LaTeX editors such as Kile and LyX.</li>
      <li xml:lang="bs">Integriraj vaše bibliografije sa LaTeX uređivačima kao što su Kile i LyX.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Integra les vostres bibliografies amb editors de LaTeX com Kile i LyX.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Integra les vostres bibliografies amb editors de LaTeX com Kile i LyX.</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Integration Ihrer Bibliografien mit LaTeX-Editoren wie Kile und LyX.</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Integrate your bibliographies with LaTeX editors such as Kile and LyX.</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Integra sus bibliografías con editores LaTeX como Kile y LyX.</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">Integroida lähdetietokantasi LaTeX-muokkaimeen kuten Kileen tai LyXiin.</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Intégrer vos bibliographies avec des éditeurs LaTeX comme Kile et LyX.</li>
      <li xml:lang="gl">Integre as súas bibliografías con editores de LaTeX como Kile e LyX.</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Integrare le tue bibliografie con gli editor LaTeX, come Kile e LyX.</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Integreer uw bibliografieën met LaTeX bewerkers zoals Kile en LyX.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Integracja bibliografii z edytorami LaTeX takimi jak Kile i LyX.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Integrar as suas bibliografias com os editores de LaTeX, como o Kile e o LyX.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Integrar suas bibliografias com os editores de LaTeX, como o Kile e o LyX.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Integrovať vaše bibliografie s editormi LaTeX ako Kile a LyX.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Integrera bibliografierna med Latex-editorer såsom Kile och LyX</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">Kaynakçalarınızı Kile ve LyX gibi LaTeX düzenleyicileri ile bütünleştirin.</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Інтегрувати ваші бібліографії з редакторами LaTeX, зокрема Kile та LyX.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxIntegrate your bibliographies with LaTeX editors such as Kile and LyX.xx</li>
      <li>Import your Zotero library.</li>
      <li xml:lang="bs">Uvoz vaše Zotero biblioteke.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Importa la vostra biblioteca de Zotero.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Importa la vostra biblioteca de Zotero.</li>
      <li xml:lang="cs">Importovat vaši knihovnu Zotero</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Import Ihrer Zotero-Bibliothek.</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Import your Zotero library.</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Importa su librería Zotero.</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">Tuoda Zotero-kirjastosi.</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Importer une bibliothèque Zotero.</li>
      <li xml:lang="gl">Importe a súa biblioteca de Zotero.</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Importare la tua raccolta Zotero.</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Uw Zotero bibliotheek importeren.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Importowanie bibliotek Zotero.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Importar a sua biblioteca do Zotero.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Importar sua biblioteca do Zotero.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Importovať vašu knižnicu Zotero.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Importera ett Zotero-bibliotek.</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">Zotero kütüphanenizi İçe Aktarın.</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Імпортувати дані з вашої бібліотеки Zotero.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxImport your Zotero library.xx</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-CN">导入您的 Zotero 仓库。</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <url type="homepage">https://userbase.kde.org/KBibTeX</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugs.kde.org/enter_bug.cgi?format=guided&amp;product=kbibtex</url>
  <url type="help">http://docs.kde.org/development/en/extragear-office/kbibtex/index.html</url>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://cdn.kde.org/screenshots/kbibtex/kbibtex-kf5.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <project_group>KDE</project_group>
  <provides>
    <binary>kbibtex</binary>
  </provides>
</component>
